{
    "id": "4e2d97aa4de7430abe4aaf34b5aef38b",
    "title": "Would vs. Should",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mary ………………………….. arrive soon. She left office at",
            "description": "We use should to indicate possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. we ask for help?",
            "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion.",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. be acquitted.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "People …………………….. obey the law.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… done this to me.",
            "description": "Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't have",
                "shouldn't have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. wake up early if there was a good reason to.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. be grateful if you could help me.",
            "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you like something to drink?",
            "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. get that mole examined.",
            "description": "Should shows necessity or obligation. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………… apologize to him for behaving like that.",
            "description": "Should shows necessity or obligation. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. have wished him on his birthday, but I forgot.",
            "description": "Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. have behaved like that.",
            "description": "Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.Should have + past participle is used to criticize people for doing or not doing things.",
            "answers": [
                "would not",
                "should not"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}